邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural
萨姆
Sammy.
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子
Take your brother outside as fast as you can.
快 迪恩 快跑
Now, Dean. Go!
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
He hasn't been home in a few days.
我发过誓再也不猎魔了
l swore I was done hunting.
我一个人没法完成
l can't do this alone.
不 杰西
No! Jess!
我想他想让我们继续他的工作
I think Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
就是 救助他人 猎杀恶魔
You know, saving people, hunting things.
不 我得找出杀杰西卡的凶手
No. I gotta find Jessica's killer.
《邪恶力量》
(密苏里州 圣路易市)
收到
Roger that.
大家注意 我们找到受害人了
Be advised, we found the victim.
她还活着
She's alive.
没事了 没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
在里面 在里面
In there.In there.
进去看看
Choke Team let's go.
站住 别动 扔了那把刀
Freeze! Don't move!Drop the knife.
把头抬起来
Keep your hands where I see them!
扔了它
Drop it.
- 转过来 - 快 快
- Hold it right there! - Come on, come on!
就现在
Now.
慢慢的
Nice and easy.
按我说的做
Do it.
(一个星期前)
好吧 我想我们能在午饭前到达图凯瑞然后向南开
All right. l figure we hit Tucumcari by lunch, then head south...
顺利的话半夜就能到达
bisbee...then Bisbee by midnight.
什么时候变得跟个女人一样了
Sam wears women's underwear.
- 我在听 我只是很忙 - 忙着做什么
- l've been listening, l'm just busy. - Busy doing what?
读我的邮件
Reading e-mails.
- 谁发给你的邮件 - 我斯坦福的朋友
- E-mails from who? - From my friends at Stanford.
你在说笑吧 你还在和你的大学同学联系吗
You're kidding. You still keep in touch with your college buddies?
- 为什么不 - 那么
- Why not? - Well...
你和他们说过你吗
what exactly do you tell them?
关于你要去那里 你在做过什么
You know? About where you've been, what you've been doing.
我告诉他们我正和我哥一起汽车旅行
I tell them l'm on a road trip with my big brother.
我只是告诉他们我需要时间安抚自己
I tell them l needed some time off after Jess.
那么你对他们撒谎了
Oh, so you lie to them.
不 我只是没告诉他们全部
No. I just don't tell them everything.
但那就叫撒谎
Yeah, that's called lying.
兄弟 这我能理解 告诉他们真相是不太好
I get it. Telling them the truth is far worse.
那我该做什么 把我的朋友都吓跑吗
So, what am l supposed to do? Just cut everybody out of my life?
- 你认真的吗 - 听着 这的确很糟糕
- You're serious? - Look, it sucks, but...
但做这样的工作 你不可能和普通人很亲近
a job like this, you can't get close to people.
是你自己不擅社交 你知道吗
You're kind of antisocial, you know that?
好吧 随你怎么说
Yeah, whatever.
- 天啊 - 怎么了
- God. - What?
这是我朋友瑞贝卡·沃伦发来的邮件
This e-mail from this girl Rebecca Warren, one of those friends of mine.
她漂亮吗
She hot?
我和她还有她哥扎克是同学
I went to school with her and her brother Zach.
她说扎克因为谋杀罪正被控告
She says Zach's been charged with murder.
因为杀害他女朋友而被捕
Arrested for killing his girlfriend.
瑞贝卡说她哥哥没做过 但是
Rebecca says he didn't do it...
但看来警察有着比较充足的证据
but it sounds like the cops have a pretty good case.
兄弟 你到底和什么样的家伙混在一起
Dude, what kind of people you hanging out with?
不 我了解扎克 他绝不会杀人
No, I know Zach. He's no killer.
也许你像他一样 都有所隐瞒
Yeah, well, maybe you know Zach as well as he knows you.
他们在圣路易市 我们走
They're in St.Louis. We're going.
我为你的朋友感到难过
Look, sorry about your buddy, okay?
但这不是我们该解决的问题
This does not sound like our kind of problem.
这是我们的问题 他们是我的朋友
It is. They're my friends.
圣路易市在我们身后400公里 Sam
St.Louis is 400 miles behind us, Sam.
- 我的天啊 萨姆 - 这不是小贝基
- Oh, my God. Sam. - Well, if it isn't little Becky.
好吧 你喜欢叫什么就叫什么
And you know what you can do with that "little Becky" crap.
- 我收到你的邮件了 - 我没想到你会来这里
- l got your e-mail. - l didn't think that you would come.
我是迪恩 他哥哥
Dean. Older brother.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我们是来帮忙的 看看我们能做什么
We're here to help.Whatever we can do.
进来
Come in.
房间很漂亮
Nice place.
这是我父母的
It's my parents'.
过去我只是周末才来这里渡假的 但当这事情发生后
I was crashing here for the long weekend when everything happened.
我决定这学期休学 等扎克没事之后我看离开
I decided to take the semester off. I'm gonna stay until Zach's free.
- 那你的亲人呢 - 他们在巴黎住了半年
- Where are your folks? - They live in Paris for half the year...
现在他们为了审讯正赶来这里
so they're on their way home now for the trial.
你们要点啤酒或其它什么
You guys want a beer?
- 谢了 - 不用了
- Hey. - No thanks.
告诉我们到底发生了什么事
So tell us what happened.
好吧 扎克回到家 他发现艾米丽被绑在椅子上
Well... Zach, he came home, and he found Emily tied to a chair.
她被人殴打过 鲜血淋淋 已经没有呼吸 所以他…
And she was beaten up and bloody, and she wasn't breathing, and so he
他打911 警察赶来了 可是
He called 911 and the police, they showed up and-
他们逮捕了他
And they arrested him.
但实际是 如果是扎克杀害了艾米丽
But the thing is, the only way that Zach could have killed Emily...
那么只能说明他能够同时身处两地
is if he was in two places at the same time.
警察有一盘录象带
The police, they have a video.
是从十字路口录象里头剪辑下来的
lt's from the security tape from across the street.
上面记录显示扎克十点半回了家
And it shows Zach coming home at 10:30.
艾米丽就在那后被杀
Now, Emily was killed just after that.
但我可以发誓他那时正和我一起 喝啤酒直到半夜
But l swear, he was here with me having a few beers until at least after midnight.
我们可以去看看扎克家的犯罪现场吗
You know, maybe we could see the crime scene.
- 扎克的家 - 可以吗
- Zach's house. - We could.
这样你们能做些什么呢
I mean, why?I mean, what could you do?
我不行 但迪恩是警察
Well, me, not much. But Dean's a cop.
- 实际上我是侦探 - 真的吗 哪里的
- A detective, actually. - Really? Where?
亚利桑那州 比斯比
Bisbee, Arizona.
但我现在在休假
But l'm off duty now.
我不明白为什么你们对我那么好 我真的不明白
You guys, it's so nice to offer, but I just-l don't know.
贝克 听着 我知道扎克没杀人
Beck, look, l know Zach didn't do this.
现在我们得证明他无罪
Now, we have to find a way to prove that he's innocent.
那好吧
Okay.
我去拿钥匙
I'm gonna go get the keys.
兄弟 看来你对你的朋友很坦白
You're a real straight shooter with your friends.
听着 扎克和贝基 需要我们的帮助
Look, Zach and Becky need our help.
可我认为这不是我们该处理的问题
l don't think this is our kind of problem.
你是说一个人同时出现在两地吗 那我们就查到底
Two places at once?We've looked into less.
你们觉得这么做合适吗
You're sure this is okay?
没问题 我是执法者
Yeah. l am an officer of the law.
贝基 你想呆在外面吗
Beck, you wanna wait outside?
不 我想帮忙
No, I wanna help.
告诉我们警察还说了什么
Tell us what else the police said.
好吧 没有闯入的迹象
Well, there's no sign of a break-in.
他们说是艾米丽让凶手进门的
They say that Emily let her attacker in.
律师们也都在考虑怎么样减少刑罚
The lawyers, they're already talking about plea-bargain.
噢 天啊
Oh, God.
听着 贝基 如果扎克没那么做 那就是其他人干的…
Look, Beck, if Zach didn't do this, it means someone else did.
能想起是谁吗
Any idea who?
对了 这有些事情 大概一星期前 有人破门而入
There was something. About a week before, somebody broke in here.
偷了些扎克的衣服
They stole some clothes. Zach's clothes.
但是警察他们把这不当回事
The police, they don't think it's anything.
我的意思是我们离市中心没那么远
I mean, we're not that far from downtown.
有时候会遭到抢劫
Sometimes people get robbed.
你知道吗 这狗以前很温顺
You know, that used to be the sweetest dog.
怎么啦
What happened?
它变了
He just changed.
你还记得它什么时候开始变的呢
Do you remember when he changed?
就在凶案发生那个时间
I guess around the time of the murder.
扎克女朋友被杀时
So the neighbor's dog went psycho...
邻居家的狗像疯了似地乱叫
right around the time Zach's girlfriend was killed.
动物通常对超自然现象很敏感
Animals can sense the paranormal.
也许它是看到了些什么
Yeah, maybe Fido saw something.
所以你现在觉得是我们的问题了吧
So you think maybe this is our kind of problem?
这还不能确定
No, probably not.
但我们得看看录象带确定一下
But we should look at the security tape just to make sure.
- 是的 - 恩
- Yeah. - Yeah.
那个录象呢
So the tape, the security footage?
也许你的律师能弄到它 我没那权限
Think your lawyers could get it?I don't have that jurisdiction.
我有带子 我不想在警察前说错什么
I've already got it. l didn't wanna say something in front of the cop.
我从律师的桌上偷到了 我只想自己看看
I stole it off the lawyer's desk.I just had to see it for myself.
很好
All right.
我会想你的
I'm miss you.
- 他们为什么要送你去呢 - 因为我是最棒的啊
- Why do they always have to send you? - Because I'm the best.
我知道 所以我想你留在家里
Well, l know. That's why I want you to stay home.
我只是去一趟堪萨斯城
It's just Kansas City.
我明晚就回来 回来弥补你
Be home tomorrow night and make it up to you.
最好是这样
You'd better.
他出现了
Here he comes.
22点04分 这刚过十点
22:04, that's just after 10.
你说了死亡时间大概是在十点半
You said time of death was about 10:30.
我的律师找了几个视频专家
Our lawyers hired some kind of video expert.
他说录象带没问题
He says the tape's authentic.
没有做手脚
It wasn't tampered with.
贝克 我们能喝点啤酒吗
Beck, can we take those beers now?
喔 当然可以
Oh, sure.
嘿 也拿点三明治 好吗
Hey... Maybe some sandwiches too?
你当这里是什么地方啊 餐厅吗
What do you think this is, Hooters?
- 你看到了什么吗 - 来看看这个
- l wish. What is it? - Check this out.
也许只是摄影机的反光
Maybe it's just a camera flare.
可不象我看过的摄影机的反光
That's not like any flare l've ever seen.
许多文明都认为照相能捕捉到灵魂
A lot of cultures believe a photo can catch a glimpse of the soul.
还记得那条发狂的狗吗 也许它就是看到了这个
Remember that dog? Maybe he saw this.
也许这是另外一个邪恶的扎克 只是外表和他一样而已
Maybe this is a dark double of Zach's, something that looks like him but isn't.
- 就象死灵 - 是的
- Like a doppelgnger. - Yeah.
这能解释他为什么同时出现在两地
That would sure explain how he was in two places at once.
亲爱的是我
Honey? It's me.
客户最后一刻取消了会面
The client cancelled at the last minute.
我打电话了 你怎么不接
I called. Why didn't you answer?
琳赛
Lindsay?
没事的 琳赛 我回来了
It's okay, Lindsay. It's me.
求你了不要再伤害我 放过我吧
Please don't hurt me anymore. Leave me alone.
好吧 才五点半 我们来这儿干吗
All right. So, what are we doing here at 5:30 in the morning?
我发现一件事
I realized something.
根据录像带显示 凶手进去后却没出来
The videotape shows the killer going in, but not coming out.
- 所以他是从后门出来的 - 是的
- So he came out the back door? - Right.
一定有轨迹可以跟踪 警察根本不会追查的轨迹
So there should be a trail to follow.A trail the police would never pursue.
因为他们以为凶手没离开 他们在里面抓到了你的朋友Zach
Because they think the killer never left. They caught your friend Zach inside.
我还是不明白我们五点半在这儿干吗
I still don't know what we're doing here at 5:30 in the morning.
血迹 凶手有经过这里
Blood. Somebody came this way.
就那点儿痕迹吧 我这边什么也没有
Maybe the trail ends.i don't see anything here.
- 发生了什么 - 他企图杀害他的妻子
- What happened? - He tried to kill his wife.
- 把她绑起来殴打她 - 真的吗
- Tied her up and beat her. - Really?
我经常看到他早上去工作 和他的妻子道别
I used to see him going to work in the morning. He'd wave, say hello.
他看起来是个好人
He seemed like such a nice guy.
- 嘿 还记得我说过这不是我们的问题吗 - 记得
- Hey. Remember when l said this wasn't our kind of problem? - Yeah.
- 可现在一定是我们的事了 - 你查到什么
- Definitely our kind of problem. - What did you find out?
我问了到现场的第一个警察 他也听了Alex的故事
I just talked to the patrolman who heard this guy Alex's story.
很明显这个家伙出公差后正开车回家
The dude was driving home
而当时他老婆正被人袭击
from a trip when his wife was attacked.
- 他同时在两地 - 对
- So he was two places at once? - Exactly.
然后别人看到他在自己家里 警察认为他胡说
Then he sees himself in the house.Cops say he's a nut job.
两起同样手法袭击自己爱人的案件
Two dark doubles attacking loved ones in exactly the same way.
也应该是同一人做的
Could be the same thing doing it too.
变形人 某种能把自己变成其它人的东西
Shapeshifter? Something that can make itself look like anyone?
世界上的每种文明都有着变形者的传说
Every culture has a shapeshifter lore.
传说中的生物能把自己变成动物或人
Legends of creatures who transform themselves into animals or other men.
对 幻兽人 狼人
Right. Skinwalkers, werewolves.
同一街区的两起袭击事件
We got two attacks within blocks of each other.
我想这里有个变形者要对付
I'm guessing we got a shapeshifter problem.
让我提个问题
Let me ask you this
这些传说中的变形人他们会飞吗
In all this shapeshifter lore, can any of them fly?
据我所知没有 我在这里发现了些痕迹
Not that I know of.l picked up a trail here.
有人从这栋楼的后面溜了出来从这条路跑了
Someone ran out of the back of this building, headed off this way.
- 就象你朋友的家一样 - 是的 就象扎克的家
- Just like your friend's house. - Yeah. And just like at Zach's house...
但痕迹突然消失了
the trail suddenly ends.
不管怎样它就是消失了
I mean, whatever it is just disappeared.
可能有条其它的路可以溜掉
Well, there's another way to go.
往地下
Down.
我打赌这也通向扎克的家
I bet this runs right by Zach's house too.
这个变形者能利用下水道系统到这周围
The shapeshifter could be using the sewer system to get around.
你说对了
I think you're right.
看看这个
Look at this.
哦 这是受害者身上的
Is this from his victims?
我刚有个恶心的想法
I just had a sick thought.
当那个变形者变身的时候
When the shapeshifter changes shape,
也许这就是它脱落的
maybe it sheds.
那太恶心了
That is sick.
我从老爸那里学来一样
One thing I learned from Dad:
无论它是那种变形者一定有种方法可以杀了它
No matter what kind of shapeshifter it is, there's one sure way to kill it.
- 用银子弹射穿它的心脏 - 对
- Silver bullet to the heart. - That's right.
我是萨姆
This is Sam.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我们在扎克家附近 我们查出了点眉目
Near Zach's, checking some things out.
请停止 因为我不需要你们的帮助了
Sam, just stop, because l really...don't need your help anymore.
你说什么
What?
我告诉了我的律师 我们去了现场
I told the lawyers that we went to the crime scene.
你为什么那么做
Why would you do that?
我告诉他们是因为我和警察陪着
I said we were with a policeman...
他们核对了身份
an the chacked it out
说根本就没有叫迪恩·温彻斯特的警察
and they told me that there is no detective Dean Winchester.
- 贝克 - 我不明白你为什么要对我撒那样的谎
- Beck.  -I don't get why you would lie to me.
- 我们想帮你 - 哦 想帮我
- We're trying to help. - Oh, trying to help?
你们意识到那是受保护的现场吗
Do you realize that was a sealed crime scene?
那么做只可能让扎克的案子更糟
This could have ruined Zach's case.
贝克 我很抱歉 可是
l'm sorry, but
再见了 萨姆
No. Goodbye, Sam.
我也不想说 可我早说过会这样的
I hate to say it, but that's exactly what I'm talking about.
你对你的朋友撒谎 因为你知道他们了解你后
You lie to your friends because if they knew the real you
他们会害怕
they'd be freaked.
如果我换作你... 那事情就会简单多了
It's just... It'd be easier if...
- 嘿 兄弟 - 这不是象或不象我们不是普通人
- lf I was like you. - Hey, like it or not, we are not like other people.
我要告诉你一件事这件事
But l'll tell you one thing, this whole gig...
你要昂首面对
it aingt without perks.
- 我觉得我们靠近它的巢穴了 - 你为什么那么说
- Think we're close to its lair. - Why do you say that?
因为在你右边又有一堆黏黏的恶心的脱皮
Because there's another puke-inducing pile next to your face.
噢 我的天那
Oh, God.
看起来它住这里有阵子了
Looks like it's lived here for a while.
谁知道他犯了多少次凶杀案啊
Who knows how many murders he's gotten away with.
迪恩
Dean!
抓住这个狗娘养的
Get the son of a bitch!
好的 我们分头追
All right, let's split up.
好的 我们在里面汇合
All right. I'll meet you on the other side.
- 是吗 - 我知道
- Yes. - Oh, I know.
嘿
Hey.
- 找到了吗 - 不 它溜掉了
- Anything? - No, he's gone.
好吧 让我们回到车上去
All right, let's get back to the car.
你认为他找到了另一条下水道吗
You think he found another way underground?
有可能你有钥匙
Yeah, probably. You got the keys?
爸爸是不是有次在圣安东尼奥对付过变形者
Hey, didn't Dad once face a shapeshifter in San Antonio?
那是在奥斯顿
No, it was Austin.
后来知道那不是变形者
And it turned out not to be a shapeshifter. lt was a thought-form.
那只是思维形式 的一个心境投射 记得吗
A psychic projection, remember?
记得 给你
Oh, right.Here you go.
别动哦 你对他做了什么
Don't move!What have you done with him?
兄弟 怎么啦 是我啊
Dude, chill. lt's me, all right?
不 我不那么想
l don't think so.
- 把我哥哥弄那里去了 - 你这样会打死他的
- Where's my brother? - You're about to shoot him.
- 萨姆 冷静点 - 你用左手接住钥匙
- Calm down. - You caught those keys with your left.
你的肩膀应该是受了伤的
Your shoulder was hurt.
是的 可现在好多了你想要我干吗 哭吗
Yeah, it's better. You want me to cry?
你不是我哥
You're not my brother.
好啊 那你怎么不开枪 因为你不确定
Why don't you pull the trigger, then.Because you're not sure.
- 兄弟 你了解我的 - 不要
- Dude, you know me. - Don't.
我哥他在那里
Where is he?
迪恩在哪里
Where's Dean?
我才不担心他
I wouldn't worry about him.
- 我只担心你 - 他在那里
- l'd worry about you. - Where is he?
其实你并不关心这个
You don't really wanna know.
我对你们家一清二楚
I swear, the more l learn about your family...
我觉得我过得并不好
I thought I came from a bad background.
你说什么 你能了解我们的想法吗
What do you mean, learn?
他和你之间有问题
He sure got issues with you.
你上了大学
You got to go to college.
而他只能呆在家
He had to stay home.
我的意思是我只能呆在家里 和爸爸一起
I mean, l had to stay home. With Dad.
你以为我没有自己的梦想吗
You don't think l had dreams of my own?
但老爸需要我
But Dad needed me.
你跑哪里去了
Where the hell were you?
我哥哥在那里
Where is my brother?
我就是你的哥哥
l'm your brother.
看 从我内心深处…
See, deep down,
我很嫉妒你
l'm just jealous.
你有朋友 有你自己的生活
You got friends. You could have a life.
我 我只知道我自己是个怪物
Me? l know I'm a freak.
所有的人迟早都会离开我
And sooner or later, everybody's gonna leave me.
- 你在说什么 - 你离开了我
- What are you talking about? - You left.
爸爸托付我每件事我都尽力完成 可他还是弃我而去
Hell, I did everything Dad asked me to, and he ditched me too.
没有任何解释 什么都没有
No explanation, nothing. Just:
离开了我 让我和你这混蛋在一起
Left me with your sorry ass.
但是我的生活
But still, this life...
终会有转机的
it's not without its perks.
我遇到了很漂亮诱人的美女
I meet the nicest people.
就象小贝基 你知道的 迪恩如果有机会一定会泡她
Like little Becky. You know Dean would bang her if he had the chance.
让我们看看会发生什么吧
Let's see what happens.
- 嗨 - 我知道你要说什么
- Oh, hi. - l know what you're gonna say.
- 哦 是吗 - 也不一定很准确
- Oh, you do? - Well, no, not exactly.
但让我猜猜看
But l can take a guess:
给我滚蛋
"Get off my porch"?
对 我会那么说
That's about right.
我承认 我们撒谎了 我想我要来解释一下
I admit it, we lied.Thought l'd try to explain myself.
萨姆叫我别来
Sam told me not to come, but I thought:
但是我想还是该来试试
"What the hell? I have to try."
该死的
Damn it.
你最好是萨姆 而不是那个怪物
That better be you, Sam, and not that freak of nature.
是我 他以你的样子去瑞贝卡的家了
Yeah, it's me. He went to Rebecca's, looking like you.
看起来他还不笨
Well, he's not stupid.
他选了个比较帅的样子
He picked the handsome one.
所以你是说有这样的怪物
So you're saying that there's something out there
他变成我哥哥的样子
that made itself look like my brother.
恩
hmm.
- 你怎么称呼它来着 - 变形者
- What did you call it? - A shapeshifter.
是的 也许我们疯了
Yeah. Maybe we're crazy.
但可能我们是正确的
But what if we're not?
你自己也那么说扎克同时在两个地方出现
Look, you said it yourself that Zach was in two places at once.
- 告诉我这怎么可能发生呢 - 好吧 那么这个东西
- Tell me how that could happen. - Okay, so this thing...
他可以让自己变成任何人吗
it can make itself look like anybody?
对
That's right.
哦 那它象什么 一个完全的怪物吗
Well, what is it? Like a genetic freak?
也许
Maybe.
可能进化中会有突变
Evolution is about mutation, right?
所以也许这个东西以人的形态出生
So maybe this thing was born human...
但却不是人类
but was different.
丑恶而且憎恨一切
Hideous and hated.
直到他学会变成某个人
Until he learned to become someone else.
对 就是这样
Yeah, that's the thing.
他不只是看上去象你 他就是你
He didn't just look like you, he was you...
或者说他在变成你
or he was becoming you.
你什么意思我不清楚
What do you mean?
就想象他在复制 你的想法和记忆
It's like he was downloading your thoughts and memories.
- 你是指复制思维 - 是的 就象那样
- You mean like the Vulcan Mind Meld? - Yes, something like that.
也许这就是为什么 他不杀掉我们的原因
Maybe that's why he doesn't just kill us.
他需要我们活着
Maybe he needs to keep us alive...
- 心灵感应 - 手给我
- ...for the psychic connection. - Hands.
快点 我们得离开这 他已经到瑞贝卡的家了
Yeah. Come on, we gotta go.He's probably at Rebecca's already.
来吧 我们得找个电话 报警
Come on. We gotta find a phone, call the police.
喔 喔 你想让我上通缉令吗
Whoa, whoa, whoa.You're gonna put an APB out on me.
对不起 往这边走
Sorry.This way.
这很有趣
It's funny.
我开始有点了解它了 它很孤独
I kind of understand him He's all alone.
不与人亲近
Close to no one.
它想要的不过是个爱它的人
All he wants is for someone to love him.
它就象我一样
He's like me.
每个人都不时需要人的抚慰
Everybody needs a little human touch now and then.
- 身为异类的感觉太难受了 - 你该走了
- lt's so hard to be different. - You should go.
你让人讨厌 快点离开这
You are disgusting!Just get out of here!
- 瑞贝卡请冷静点 - 要我冷静吗
- Rebecca, just calm down. - Oh, calm down.
- 你到底怎么回事 - 问我怎么回事
- What is wrong with you? - What's wrong with me?
- 这该问你 - 我要报警了
- What's wrong with you? - I'm calling the police.
把你手伸出来
Give me your hands!
闭嘴
Shut up!
你是个漂亮的女孩 瑞贝卡
You're a nice girl, Rebecca.
我的意思是 我喜欢你
I mean, l liked you.
相信我 这让我很难下手
Believe me, it makes this harder.
但我还是要做我该做的事
But l gotta do what I gotta do.
别动 扔了那把刀 扔了那把刀
Freeze! Drop the knife.Drop the knife!
扔了那把刀 扔了那把刀
Drop the knife!
追 追
Come on, come on!
上 上
Go! Go!
警察在房子里发现一名当地女性被绑于室
Where asquad team discovered a local woman found engaged
白人男性 年龄在24岁至30岁
her attacker a white male approximately 24 to 30years of age
警察当时发现凶手藏匿于屋内
was discovered hiding in the home
- 有枪声响起 伙计 - 这照片也太难看了
- Shots were fired... - Man, that's not even a good picture.
但足够让人认出你
It's good enough.
快走
Come on.
他们说企图谋杀 但至少我们知道
They said attempted murder.At least we know
我没杀死她
l didn't kill her.
我明早要去看看瑞贝卡 看看她还好吗
l'll check on Rebecca in the morning.
我要先找到这个帅气的魔鬼 把他打回原形
First l'm gonna find that handsome devil and kick the crap out of him.
我们没有武器 没有银子弹
We have no weapons, no silver bullets.
这个家伙扮着我的样子在街上大摇大摆 我得找到他
The guy's walking around with my face.It's personal. l wanna find him.
- 好的我们去那里找呢 - 我们从下水道入手
- Okay. Where do we look? - We could start with the sewers.
我们没有武器
We have no weapons.
他偷走了我们的枪 我们需要枪
He stole our guns. We need more.
- 汽车呢 - 我打赌他开到瑞贝卡家去了
- The car? - l bet he drove over to Rebecca's.
新闻说他只身逃跑我打赌它还停在那里
The news said he fled on foot, I bet it's still parked there.
- 一想到开走了我的车 - 走吧
- The thought of him driving my car. - Come on.
- 这气死我了 - 别着急
- That's killing me. - Let it go.
终于找到了
There she is.
看来今晚还算有件好事
Finally something went right tonight.
该死的
OH Crap.
这边 这边
This way! This way!
- 你快走 我吸引他们 - 他们会抓住你的
- You go, I'll hold them. - They'll catch you.
他们不能拘留我的
They can't hold me!
快走 快走 在瑞贝卡的家和我汇合
Just go, keep out of sight. Meet me at Rebecca's.
迪恩 别一个人去下水道
Dean! Stay out of the sewers alone!
- 我是认真的 - 好 知道了
- l mean it! - Yeah, yeah.
别动 把你的手放在我能看到的地方
Don't move! Keep your hands where l can see them.
对不起 萨姆 你了解我的性格 我不能坐以待毙
I'm sorry, Sam.You know me, l just can't wait.
- 瑞贝卡 - 那么看来有变形者是真的
- Becca? - So say this......shapeshifter is real.
可能是你疯了
By the way, you know you're crazy.
但假如它是真的
But say it is real.
你怎么阻止它
How do you stop it?
谢谢 用银子弹射穿它的心脏
Thanks. Silver bullet to the heart.
你疯了
You are crazy.
发生什么事了
What happened?
我在回家的路上有人重击了我的头
I was walking home, and everything just went white.
然后我就晕过去了
Someone hit me over the headand
我刚好醒来看到它变成了我
l wound up here...in time to see that thingturn into me.
- 这怎么可能 - 好了 没事了来吧
- How is that even possible? - Okay, okay. lt's okay.
你能走吗 好的 我们得快点 萨姆想见你
Come on. Can you walk?Okay, we gotta hurry.Sam went to see you.
你要对我做什么
What are you gonna do to me?
我不会做什么 迪恩 他会做
I'm not gonna do anything.Dean will, though.
- 警察永远也抓不到他 - 没关系
- They'll never catch him. - Oh, it doesn't matter.
杀害了他的亲弟弟
Murder in the first of his own brother?
他会在追捕中度过余下一生
He'll be hunted the rest of his life.
我必须说
I must say...
我很抱歉失去这副身体
l will be sorry to lose this skin.
你的哥哥身体很棒
Your brother's got a lot of good qualities.
你应该多谢谢他
You should appreciate him more than you do.
干杯
Cheers.
你这个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
还不赖 我的弟弟 你不是他
Not bad, little brother.You're not him.
当我们还是孩子时
Even when we were kids...
我就打得你满地爬
l always kicked your ass.
萨姆
Sam.
这就是你们一直在做的事吗
So this is what you do.
你和你的哥哥 你们到处猎杀这样的恶魔
You and your brother, you hunt down these kinds of things?
- 是的 就是这样 - 我都不敢相信
- Yeah, pretty much. - l can't believe it.
我是说当我亲眼看着你这么做 而且…
I mean, l saw it with my own eyes, and...
那学校里所有的同学 没人知道你做这个吗
I mean, does everybody at school?Nobody knows that you do this?
不
No.
那杰西卡知道吗
Did Jessica know?
不 她不知道
No, she didn't.
- 那一定很孤独 - 哦 不不 没那么糟糕
- Must be lonely. - Oh, no. No, it's not so bad.
不管怎么样 那毕竟是我家族的事业
Anyway, it What can I do?It's my family.
好吧 你知道吗扎克和我以及所有在学校的同学
Well, you know, Zach and me andeverybody at school
大家都很想念你
we really miss you.
恩 我也是
Yeah, me too.
你什么时候打电话给我呢
Well, will you call sometime?
那肯定不会太久
It might not be for a little while.
你朋友扎克怎么样了
So, what about your friend Zach?
警察开始注意到有一个叫 迪恩·温彻斯特的家伙
Cops are blaming this Dean Winchester guy
针对艾米丽的凶杀案
for Emily's murder.
在这个家伙的巢穴里找到了谋杀凶器
They found the murder weapon in the guy's lair...
还有扎克血迹斑斑的衣服
Zach's clothes stained with her blood.
现在他们觉得可能那盘监视录影带被做了手脚
Now they're thinking maybe the surveillance tape was tampered with.
瑞贝卡说扎克很快就要被无罪释放
Yeah, Becca says Zach will be released soon.
对不起 伙计
Sorry, man.
对不起什么
About what?
我真希望事情不是这样 我希望你真的是一个…
I really wish things could be different.I wish you could just be...
- 大学生 - 没事
- Joe College. - lt's okay.
你知道吗 事实上斯坦福大学 我始终没有适应它
You know, truth is, even at Stanford, deep down, l never really fit in.
因为你是个怪胎
Well, that's because you're a freak.
是的 谢谢 其实我也是个变态
Yeah, thanks. Well, l'm a freak too.
我会和你一直同路
I'm right there with you all the way.
是的 我知道你会
Yeah, l know you are.
- 你知道吗 我得说 我肯定会怀念 - 怀念什么
- You know, I gotta say, I'm sorry I'm gonna miss it. - Miss what?
谁有机会亲眼看到自己死掉啊
How many chances am l gonna have to see my own funeral?